apartmenthunterz.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy / Apartment Hunters

Effective Date: 9/20/2016

This privacy policy applies to www.ApartmentHunterZ.com owned and operated by Apartment Hunters Inc. («ApartmentHunterZ.com»). This privacy policy describes how ApartmentHunterZ.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website: www.ApartmentHunterZ.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

ApartmentHunterZ.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the ApartmentHunterZ.com. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

This policy will let you know:

  * What personal information is collected from you
  * Tracking Technologies and how they are used
  * How your information is used
  * Who is collecting your information
  * With whom your information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your information
  * How you can access, update or delete your information
  * The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
  * Links to 3rd Party Sites
  * Social Media Widgets
  * How ApartmentHunterZ.com protects children's privacy
  * Changes to this privacy policy
  * Contact Us

## What personal information is collected from you

The ApartmentHunterZ.com collects information in several ways from different parts of our website.

Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, we ask for your name and email address. The system will also ask for your street address, city, state/province, zip/postal code, country, telephone number, and the URL of your website, although only fields that are marked with an asterisk (*) on the registration field are required. This information is used solely to assist you in navigating the system by automatically filling in certain forms (such as the Vacancy posting form) with your information so that you don't have to continually re-enter it. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to ApartmentHunterZ.com – you have a username and are able to take full advantage of the many offerings of the ApartmentHunterZ.com.

In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place vacancies or take advantage of the other features of the ApartmentHunterZ.com. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Every page within the ApartmentHunterZ.com includes a link to this Privacy Policy.

## Tracking Technologies and how they are used

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by apartmenthunterz.com and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers (Google Analytics, LiveChat). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes:

  1. To store and sometimes track information about you
  2. To identify and label all «new» vacancies since your last visit to the site
  3. Optionally to permanently save your password on your computer so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site
  4. To enable you to «checklist and compare» vacancies that you want to mark for future retrieval and viewing

Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. (See «What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your information» for more information on cookies.) 

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and search preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner uses cookies to gather information about your activities on this and other Websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may [opt-out by clicking here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

## How your information is used

ApartmentHunterZ.com website is an information resource for individuals looking for rental properties. A user can navigate limited portions of our Site without disclosing any personal information. To get the full benefit of our services we require users to create an account. When you select to sign up for an account, we request your name, phone number, address and credit card information in order to find you the best apartments in your area.

We also use your email to send you rental search results when you express your choice to receive them. We do not share your email address with third parties. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at support@apartmenthunterz.com

As is true of most websites, ApartmentHunterZ.com may also collect certain information automatically from visitors to, and customers of the Site such as Internet addresses and store it in log files. This Website Navigational Information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, to analyze trends, to track users' movements around the Site, and to administer our Site in order to constantly improve the quality of the Site and our Service. We may also track and analyze individual usage and volume statistical information («Aggregated Information») from our visitors and customers. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you.

## Who is collecting your information

When you are asked for personal information on the ApartmentHunterZ.com, you are sharing that information with the ApartmentHunterZ.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of the ApartmentHunterZ.com. For example, when you enter personal information on the Vacancy posting form, this information will generally be included in your Vacancy, unless specifically stated otherwise. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

To request removal of your personal information from a public forum, contact us here. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

## With whom your information may be shared

As a general rule, ApartmentHunterZ.com will not disclose any of your personal information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.

ApartmentHunterZ.com may disclose personal information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of the ApartmentHunterZ.com or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of the ApartmentHunterZ.com, other users of the ApartmentHunterZ.com, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. ApartmentHunterZ.com may disclose or access personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. In certain situations, ApartmentHunterZ.com may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. If ApartmentHunterZ.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We may also provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We post customer testimonials on our website which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us here.

## What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your information

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the ApartmentHunterZ.com, but you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services of the ApartmentHunterZ.com that require registration in order to participate. These services include the identification of new vacancies that have been posted since your last visit, auto-filling of the login form, and the Comparison Shopper feature. You can still use most of the features of the ApartmentHunterZ.com even if you do not accept cookies.

The ApartmentHunterZ.com does not sell, rent or trade user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service.

## How you can access, update or delete your information

Upon request, ApartmentHunterz.com will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us here. We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may edit or delete your user profile at any time by clicking on the «My Profile» link or graphic provided by the system once you are logged in. Once you have logged onto the system during a given session, wherever you go on the ApartmentHunterZ.com, your information will stay with you until or unless you click on the «Sign Out» link, which is accessible from within the «My Profile» screen. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

If you are a previously registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may obtain it by email by using our «Forgot Password» feature. Click the button on any login page to request that your password would be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means.

Your ApartmentHunterZ.com account can be deleted, but doing so will result in not being able to access any of the features of the program that require user registration.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information

Other than the administrator of the ApartmentHunterZ.com or other authorized personnel of the ApartmentHunterZ.com, you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your user registration is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. ApartmentHunterZ.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. As an extra security precaution, you may want to logoff once you have completed a session in the ApartmentHunterZ.com. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, ApartmentHunterZ.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us here

## Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our Site includes links to other Websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of ApartmentHunterZ.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Website you visit. 

Our Website includes Social Media Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## How ApartmentHunterZ.com protects children's privacy

ApartmentHunterZ.com is a general audience website. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. ApartmentHunterZ.com does not knowingly collect information from anyone under 13 years of age. If we find that we have mistakenly collected information from a child we will take the necessary steps to delete the information immediately. If you feel that we have collected information from a user under the age of 13 please contact us and we will delete it.

## Changes to this privacy policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

  * Online: submit your request here
  * Email: support@apartmenthunterz.com
  * Mail: 32565 Golden Lantern St, Dana Point, CA 92629
